[♪ slow instrumental music playing]
[♪ "Brand New Day" by Demi Lovato playing]
♪ I'm gonna run so fast
till I can't breathe ♪
♪ I can't breathe ♪
- ♪ Come along and follow me ♪
- ♪ Follow me ♪
♪ Let's make some noise
Like we never did before ♪
♪ It's a brand new day ♪
♪ Don't you see me ♪
- Hey, come on, man.
- Sorry, sorry.
♪ On my way ♪
♪ So completely ♪
♪ This time I'm gonna sing
and you're gonna hear it ♪
♪ This time I'm gonna show you
that I got the spirit ♪
[over speakers] ♪ It's a brand new day ♪
♪ And I'm feelin' good ♪
Oh, my God! Look, look,
there's the cabins.
And there's a stage over there. [chuckles]
We're here!
Finally.
I'm exactly where I'm supposed to be.
[chuckles] Mom, Dad.
Literally all of our favorite artists
spent their summers here.
I mean, Camp Rock is basically
a historical landmark.
Thank you so much.
Well, we're just glad you two
get to spend more time together.
Mmm.
Sage, stop.
[Sage] Desi, come on.
How are you not geeking out right now?
I mean, this has been
our dream for, like, ever.
Is this how it's gonna be all of summer?
I mean, you barely even talking to me?
Well, I figured that's how you'd want it,
since you broke up the band.
Look, I know you
and you're just as excited as I am
whether you admit it or not.
[♪ upbeat rock music playing]
Cliff, son. Remember what we worked on.
Self-control in group settings, okay?
[imitating Yoda] "Control myself, I must!
For in restraint true strength lies."
- Is that Yoda?
- Yeah.
[♪ upbeat rock music continues]
Um, Rosie, darling,
are-are we absolutely sure about this?
You said I could come to Camp Rock
if I brought my cello.
[sighs]
Hey, guys. I'm Desi.
[♪ playing rock music]
Sick.
- Hey.
Looks like we're bunkmates.
- I'm Sage.
- I'm Rosie.
I called bottom bunk,
but the top bunk is all yours.
Could we discuss that? Actually, I'd love
the bottom bunk if possible.
Sometimes I wake up and check on my cello,
you know, like people do
with their babies.
Huh.
Uh, you know what?
On second look, I might actually be able
to fit it up there with me, so...
No, no, no, no, no. No, it's okay.
I would never separate a girl from
her emotional support cello.
Trust me, I get it.
Look who came to camp with me.
- [Sage laughs]
- Thanks.
[♪ drums beating in distance]
- [crowd chanting] Camp Rock!
- It can't be.
Camp Rock!
[chuckles]
[Sage] I can't believe
they still do this here.
- I thought it was a myth.
- Oh, yeah.
Every year. Oh, I'm Callie Banks. Bunk 9G.
- No way, me too. I'm Sage.
- [crowd] Camp Rock!
So we just got done watching
the Camp Rock stomp.
Oh, my God, Maddie! We love you!
Maddie!
[Maddie] Hey.
- Wait, is that...
- "thatBaddieMaddie'09!"?
She has, like, a cabillion followers.
She thinks she runs this place.
Okay, let's dance.
Yeah. Can you take this?
This too.
She brought her backup dancers?
Maddie's Baddies?
[♪ upbeat music playing]
She must be the best dancer here.
Girl, not if I have
anything to say about it.
Okay.
[Sage chuckles]
[♪ music continues]
[crowd cheering]
♪ It's been a long and crazy road
but it led us back to home ♪
♪ What didn't kill us
Only made us stronger ♪
♪ We've been around the world and back ♪
♪ Lots of stories to unpack ♪
♪ Wanna hear 'em
You can come on over ♪
♪ Come over, come over ♪
♪ If you can hear it
you can come on over ♪
♪ On a long and crazy road ♪
- ♪ But it led us back to home ♪
- [grunts]
- Dude!
- What?
- You keep crossing me.
- [Lark] Cut!
[bell ringing]
So, so great, guys.
Yeah, loved when you all gave up at once.
Let's take ten!
No, you've gotta be kidding me.
[♪ upbeat music playing]
Hey, Lark.
[sighs] Hi, Shane. Hi.
You good? You seem, um,
more overly caffeinated than normal.
I'm fine. The tour is fine,
everything's fine.
[inhales] Okay, fine.
Girl Vibe is no longer available.
- Our opening act quit?
- They didn't quit, they broke up.
- They said their vibe was off.
- The vibe was off?
Jason and Nate are barely speaking
and they're here.
- [both] Yeah.
- We need to figure this out
or we're in serious trouble.
Okay, I'll just find us a new opening act.
No, you found Girl Vibe
and we saw how that turned out.
Yeah.
We'll handle the opening act
this time, okay?
Somebody had to do it.
You were out there being
Mr. Bigshot movie star
and Jason was in dad mode.
What? I am fully prepared
to rock all the time.
Hard to rock with a baby
strapped to your chest, okay?
- She knows how to rock.
- And you,
by the way, do you even know
the words to this song?
Why are you always wearing stripes
when I'm wearing stripes?
I'm not wearing stripes
all the time. This is a one time--
Enough!
We are about to begin a sold out
national tour called Reconnected.
It's gonna blow up in our faces when
you're this disconnected.
First things first,
you guys need to find a new opening act.
I think I know just the place.
[♪ upbeat music playing]
Welcome to Camp Rock!
[all cheering]
Let me ask you something.
Who's ready for the best summer ever?
[all continue cheering]
I'm Connie Torres, camp director.
And yes, Mitchie's Mom.
This camp changed Mitchie's life.
And now I run it, which means I get
a chance to watch it change yours.
[crowd cheering]
Couple quick rules, most important...
no phones.
- [all groan]
- I know, I know.
But Camp Rock is better face to face
than screen to screen.
Trust me.
- [scoffs]
- You know, when I look out at all of you,
all I can think about is all the talent
that has come through Camp Rock.
Legends are made here.
And I know that this summer
will be no different!
[all cheering]
- [engine revving]
- [gasps]
[♪ upbeat music playing]
[chattering indistinctly]
And speaking of Camp Rock legends,
let's welcome back Connect 3!
[all cheering]
- Are you kidding?
- What?
It's Shane Gray, it's Shane Gray.
- [♪ upbeat music playing]
- What's up Camp rock?
[cheering continues]
- Hello, campers.
- How's it going, campers?
Hi!
Good to see you.
[Connie] Here you go.
Camp Rock.
Man, I've missed this place.
Yeah, it is so good to be back.
[crowd cheering]
All right, let's get into
why we're here, shall we?
We have a big year ahead.
Thirty cities, sold out tour.
Crowd so loud,
you can't hear yourself think.
The only thing missing...
someone to open for us.
Ah, but not just any opener.
Someone reliable,
who won't change the set list
five minutes before showtime.
[chuckles politely]
Somebody who shows up on time.
Who doesn't need three assistants
to tune one guitar.
Someone who won't fall asleep
at rehearsals
because bedtime at home is now 8:30.
Wow, you're really doing this?
Anyway, we figured, why not come here
and find our opening act
right here, right now.
[camper] Yeah!
[Shane] All right, here's the deal.
Over the next two weeks,
there's going to be three challenges.
You get through those,
you get a shot at the Final Jam.
You will be performing
an original song written by you.
It's your chance to show us
exactly who you are.
And we're gonna be in the crowd to choose
our next tour mate.
So, no pressure,
just the chance of a lifetime
and eternal bragging rights
that you opened for Connect 3.
[cheering]
Oh, my Gosh.
[Jason] Until then, you'll be
in the very capable hands
of our tour manager, Lark.
I am so getting a raise for this.
All right, Camp Rock.
Who's ready to open for Connect 3?
[all cheering]
[♪ upbeat music playing]
♪ Oh ♪
♪ I was born with fire in my veins ♪
♪ Adrenaline's been screaming my name ♪
♪ And it's my time to shine ♪
♪ I've got my moves down
head up, hitting my mark ♪
♪ Face front, straight back
know it by heart ♪
♪ And my eye's on the prize ♪
♪ Tour bus, flashing lights
save me a spot ♪
♪ Billboards, center stage ready or not ♪
♪ 'Cause I know
I could be one in a million ♪
♪ One shot this is the moment ♪
♪ One chance
I'm gonna show them ♪
♪ Dream so close that I can touch it ♪
♪ One beat away
and I'm ready to crush it ♪
♪ One break not gonna slow down ♪
♪ Someday is happening right now ♪
♪ Dream so close
I almost got it ♪
♪ One beat away and I'm ready to rock it ♪
[siren chirps]
[♪ music continues]
[exhales]
♪ Heartbeat racing loud in my chest ♪
♪ Whispers feed the fear in my head ♪
♪ But I'm not backing down ♪
♪ Got my my game face
Deep breath ♪
♪ Keeping my cool ♪
♪ Straight lines, sharp turns
No other rules ♪
♪ I'm going to wear this crown ♪
♪ Sound check, limousine
Name on the door ♪
♪ Headline, VIPs
Screaming for more ♪
♪ 'Cause I know I can be
one in a million ♪
♪ One shot
This is the moment ♪
♪ One chance
I'm gonna show them ♪
♪ Dream so close that I can touch it ♪
♪ One beat away
and I'm ready to crush it ♪
♪ One break
Not gonna slow down ♪
♪ 'Cause someday is happening right now ♪
♪ Dream so close
I almost got it ♪
♪ One beat away and I'm ready to rock it ♪
♪ One shot ♪
♪ One chance ♪
♪ One beat away
One beat away ♪
♪ I want the spotlight
to shine in my eye ♪
♪ I wanna kick back and go with the vibe ♪
♪ One last dance and a stage ♪
♪ Making new beats
and new friends on the way ♪
♪ Right here is where I belong ♪
♪ One shot
This is the moment ♪
♪ One chance
I'm gonna show them ♪
♪ Dream so close that I can touch it ♪
♪ One beat away
and I'm ready to crush it ♪
♪ One break
Not gonna slow down ♪
[chorus] ♪ Someday is happening
Right now  ♪
♪ No, no, no ♪
♪ Dream so close
I almost got it ♪
♪ One beat away and I'm ready to rock it ♪
[both grunt]
[♪ mellow guitar music playing]
[Connie] You must be Fletch Robinson?
Yeah. Yeah, I'm sorry I'm late.
Welcome to Camp Rock.
You, sir, know how to make an entrance.
This way.
[chattering indistinctly]
The older bunk was already full
when your cousin called.
- I'm fine wherever.
- Okay, good, good.
Because this bunk
is the one that's available.
[murmuring]
Boys, this is Fletch.
Fill him in on what he missed, okay?
All right.
Is it true you came
in a cop car from jail?
♪ Fletch go fetch ♪
♪ Fletch I bet you wanna play catch ♪
♪ Fletcha, Fletch! Fletch, catch this! ♪
I'm Cliff.
[sighs]
[gasping]
Relax.
If I wanted to hurt you...
I'd wait till lights out.
♪ One shot
This is the moment ♪
♪ One chance
I'm gonna show them ♪
♪ Dreams so close
I almost got it ♪
♪ One beat away
And I'm ready to rock it ♪
- Yes! Sing it, girl!
- [gasps] Oh.
No, that wasn't singing,
that was, um, vowel support.
A technical exercise
like scales or Pilates.
It sounded like singing to me.
Impossible. I come from a long line
of classical musicians.
My parents forbid me from indulging in
recreational melody.
It leads to...
- [whispers] ...jazz.
- Call it what you want,
but it sounded good.
And I look forward to competing against
your vocal Pilates.
[chuckles] No, I am not competing.
Um, I'm a cello player.
I'm like the Wi-Fi,
essential but unnoticed.
Well, log in, girl.
I mean, I still plan on winning,
but it's not a real competition without
some real competition.
Me?
Singing?
I don't know. It just feels
so front and center.
You know, with a cello,
you're the foundation,
the candlestick supporting the flame.
To actually be the flame?
- I could never.
- I mean, you do you.
But news flash, this is Camp Rock.
Around here, even the candlesticks sing.
♪ We talk the talk
We're the kids of Camp Rock ♪
♪ We walk the walk
We talk the talk ♪
♪ We're the kids of Camp Rock ♪
[all] Whoo!
- You lose something?
- Yeah.
Yeah. Uh... Uh... Uh...
Drumsticks! The guys thought
it'd be hilarious
to chuck 'em on the roof.
[sighs] Message received.
- [thumps]
- [rattling]
- Thanks.
- [drumsticks clatter]
[whispers] Yeah.
♪ Bounce to the beat
Bounce, bounce to the beat ♪
♪ Bounce to the beat... ♪
Yo, that's been in my head
since breakfast. Do you ever get that?
Yeah, actually, I do.
Well, I'm gonna use it,
write the whole song,
perform it, win, tour.
Boom!
New life.
Good luck with that, buddy.
Buddy?
Should we harmonize later,
or is it too soon?
[scoffs]
Okay, so, you know that girl Rosie?
The goddess with the cello?
She says that for safety issues,
she avoids all cliffs.
But that's just her way
of saying that she likes me.
What's your take?
[♪ upbeat music playing]
[Connie] Come in.
[♪ upbeat music stops]
- Hi. Rosie, right?
- [Rosie] Hi.
Yes. I'd like to revise my workshop
registration, please.
Let's see. "Hard Rock Basics,
Songwriting, Center Stage 101."
Wow.
These are some adventurous choices.
You go, girl.
Consider your registration
- revised.
- [pen swishes]
Thank you very much.
[Connie chuckles lightly]
[Sage] Callie, I'm so excited
for this competition.
[chuckles] I have lots to do today.
But I still can't believe
you're not competing.
Look, I know my strengths.
I could carry a tune but dance...
[exhales] ...that's my real voice.
But Lark asked me to be her assistant.
I mean, what's the first challenge?
Sing Connect 3's biggest hit
and make it our own.
We get to show Lark who we are as artists.
[chuckles softly]
[♪ upbeat music playing]
Oh, practice rooms are open. Gotta go.
Okay, you got this.
[exhales]
Five, six, seven, eight.
One, two, three, four,
and five, six, seven, eight,
and one, two, three,
four, five, six, seven, eight, one...
Hey.
[scoffs]
Not to be the practice room police,
but there's a 30-minute limit.
Don't even worry about it, girl.
[chuckles softly] Okay.
Thing is, she's next for the room
and then he's next after that.
So if I were you,
I'd try and find another room.
But I love your whole vibe,
it's giving... [inhales]
...effort.
[snickering]
Again. Five, six, seven, eight.
[♪ playing soulful chords]
Hey, can I steal this room?
All the others are taken.
Hi, Sage. I'm doing good.
How are you?
[exhales] Please, I really need it.
Let me think about it for a second.
- No.
- Desi.
Come on, you're just messing around.
I actually have to rehearse.
The first challenge is tomorrow.
And how do you know I'm not competing?
Because every time I try
to get you to play
Battle of the Bands,
you call me a sellout with no soul.
Now, that does sound like me.
[♪ resumes playing piano]
[smacks] All right.
I'm pulling the big sister card. Out, now.
Hey, if your fancy new music school
didn't prepare you for this competition,
I don't know what half an hour
in a practice room is gonna do.
You're still mad that I left the band
to go to Anthem.
I don't know what you're talking about.
I'm pretty sure
we sound better without you.
I'm gonna be Connect 3's opening act,
and nothing's gonna throw me off my game.
Not even you.
Enjoy the room.
[footsteps receding]
[door closes]
[PA chimes]
[Lark on PA] All competing campers,
meet me in the dining hall
for the first challenge.
Let's see who you are as an artist.
I need vocals. I need star power.
I need coffee.
[♪ upbeat instrumental rock music playing]
Let's begin.
Who's first?
♪ Turn on the radio ♪
♪ As loud as it can go ♪
♪ Wanna dance until
my feet can't feel the ground ♪
♪ Say goodbye to all my fears ♪
♪ One good song they disappear ♪
♪ And nothing in the world
can bring me down ♪
[awkwardly, out of tune]
♪ Hand clapping earth-shaking ♪
♪ Heartbreaking there's no-- ♪
[confidently] ♪ Faking what you feel
when you're right at home ♪
♪ Yeah ♪
♪ Music's in my soul ♪
♪ I can hear it every day
and every night ♪
♪ It's the one thing on my mind ♪
♪ Music's got control ♪
♪ And I'm never letting go ♪
[both] ♪ No, no ♪
♪ I just wanna play my music ♪
♪ Got my six-string on my back ♪
♪ Don't need anything but that ♪
♪ Everything I want is here with me ♪
[in operatic voice]
♪ So forget that fancy car ♪
[in techno voice]
♪ I don't need to go that far ♪
[pop style singing] ♪ What's driving me
is following my dream ♪
[vocalizing] ♪ Yeah ♪
[awkwardly] ♪ Hand clapping earthshaking ♪
[confidently] ♪ Heartbreaking ♪
♪ There's no faking what you feel ♪
[R&B style singing]
♪ When you're on a roll ♪
♪ Yeah ♪
[pop style singing] ♪ Music's in my soul ♪
[R&B style singing] ♪ I can hear it ♪
[Latin American style singing]
♪ Every day and every night ♪
♪ It's the one thing on my mind ♪
- ♪ Music's got control ♪
- [rapping] ♪ Music's got control y'all ♪
♪ Never let it go, no ♪
[jazz style] ♪ Oh no, no I just wanna
play my music ♪
[rock style singing]
♪ Music's got control ♪
♪ And I'm never letting go
No, no ♪
♪ I just wanna play my music ♪
♪ All night long ♪
♪ Yeah ♪
Before I post the list
of campers moving on in the competition,
I would just like to say, you are seen.
You are enough.
Please don't freak out, 'kay?
[♪ upbeat instrumental rock music playing]
Breathe, Luke, just think.
You'll have front row seats
to someone else's dreams coming true.
[Luke sobbing]
I mean, you'll get 'em next time.
[Luke continues sobbing]
I'm so proud of you!
Wait one sec.
- Hi. [chuckles]
- Hey.
I'm just gonna steal him for a sec.
[sighs]
Desi, what are you doing here?
What does it look like I'm doing?
I'm networking.
You said you weren't even competing.
Uh, I performed, didn't I?
You crashed the auditions
in a hoodie with no plan.
Sage, you were born planning things.
I was born playing things.
It's not a competition.
This literally is a competition.
[scoffs] I'll see you
at the next challenge, sis.
Break a leg.
Maybe even break two.
For balance.
[scoffs] Ugh.
Hey, nice job back there.
- Thanks.
- But kind of stiff.
[fan whirring]
Loosen up and have fun with it.
'Kay?
'Kay.
Hello down there.
Any chance you guys could do me a solid
and go grab camp director, Connie?
Funny story,
I didn't think I was afraid of heights.
[yelling] Turns out I am.
[in normal voice] Appreciate you guys.
[yelling] You're gonna get her, right?
Welcome to Camp Rock's
songwriting workshop.
This isn't a part of the competition,
but I think it could really help.
I have been wanting
to bring this next guy here
for a while.
He is an up-and-coming singer/songwriter
and one of the most-streamed artists
of all last year.
He's also one of my favorite
Camp Rock alums.
Please welcome...
Calvin Rhodes!
[crowd applauding and cheering]
Hi, Connie.
- Amazing.
- [Connie chuckling]
Welcome, future legends.
I can't believe this is happening.
His last album changed my life.
Songwriting is all in the details, okay?
It's about the feeling under the feeling.
Don't tell me that she smiled.
Tell me that her smile
holds the promise of a thousand dreams.
Let's start smaller. Okay.
Let's pair up
and let's interview each other.
No. No, no, no, no, no.
Don't think you're getting off that easy.
I want you to interview
a camper that you haven't met before.
Now, really ask
the weird questions, dig deep,
find out what makes them tick.
Turn to the camper behind you.
Back row. Turn to the camper
on your right.
[♪ romantic guitar music playing]
- Hey.
Five, six, seven, turn.
Eight.
Hey, Desi, no songwriting for you?
No. Workshops aren't for me.
You want to be a stand-in?
I need help figuring out this transition.
Pass, I am not a dancer.
Well, if you want to open for Connect 3,
you kinda have to dance.
Nah, I'll stick with what I know.
Wow. King of the comfort zone.
Well, if you change your mind,
you know where to find me.
[exhales]
All right, let's get started.
Um...
You, tell me what you learned
about your partner.
Okay, um, hi, so my partner was Rosie.
Her favorite color
is off-white but not beige.
Her superpower is memorizing
every wrong note she has ever played,
and her favorite pet is her metronome.
- Nailed it.
- Yes!
- [Calvin] See, that's proof right there...
- Good job.
...that you don't need fireworks
to light someone up.
Simple words,
real details, that's the goal.
All right. Next volunteer.
[smacks lips]
Hey, "Mr. Please-don't-look at me."
I'm looking at ya.
Okay, um...
Well, this is Sage Scott.
Hi. [chuckles]
[Fletch] And as she just demonstrated,
her nose sort of crinkles when she laughs.
She also kinda sings
a little when she talks.
And she bites her cuticles,
or tries to make a joke
anytime she doesn't wanna
talk about something.
Hey, I've been messing with this...
this melody for a little while now.
I've never really had
any lyrics that felt right.
But I think I do now.
- Could I?
- Please do.
[indistinct chatter]
One, two, three, four.
♪ Mmm ♪
♪ Crooked smile in a campfire light ♪
♪ Eyes like embers under moonlit skies ♪
♪ She don't notice
but she shines so bright ♪
♪ She's confident
but part of her is terrified ♪
♪ She thinks no one gets it but I do ♪
♪ The highs and lows
we've both been through ♪
♪ Waiting for someone to see it too ♪
♪ Maybe tomorrow we'll wake up
on the bright side ♪
♪ Chase away all the dark nights ♪
♪ And find a way to hope ♪
♪ Maybe tomorrow ♪
♪ We'll feel something so brand new ♪
♪ Leave our past in the rear view ♪
♪ And say it's gonna get better ♪
♪ Maybe tomorrow, tomorrow ♪
[all cheering]
[all clapping]
That is how you write a song.
[clapping continues]
Okay, so maybe I am
mildly in love with him
but like in a stupid way
that'll make a great song later.
Not like a real way
where I'd ever focus on a guy
I'm only gonna know for a couple of weeks
and divert all my attention
from a competition that
could change my whole life.
[chuckles softly]
I just asked how
the workshop went, but okay.
Also, I know he liked you I mean, hello.
You said he told all of camp
that your nose crinkles! [squealing]
[both laughing]
[whispering] Also I heard
he's banned from most of Canada
and the entire state of New Jersey.
What?
It doesn't matter anyway.
He's my competition.
I... I would never...
And there's the crinkles.
[both laughing]
It's involuntary, like, hiccups.
All right, we're going
to the bonfire. Let's go.
You go.
I need to, like, get in the zone
for the second challenge.
Come on!
I just wish I knew what more I could do.
I mean, I rehearse constantly
and then Lark says I'm too polished,
that I need to have more fun.
So now I'm thinking I set aside 20 minutes
every day to just be carefree.
You want to know what I love about dance?
Hmm.
That moment, I just stop thinking
and the beat takes over.
When it's not about
nailing every move anymore.
It's about being real enough
to make people feel it with me.
And maybe that's what your music needs.
It doesn't need more practice.
It needs more you.
[sighs]
Okay, fine. I'll go.
[smacks lips] Okay,
I'll meet you out there.
Oh, save me a seat with a backrest
before all the percussion kids snag them.
- I got you.
- Thanks.
[door creaks]
[door closes]
[floorboard creaking]
[♪ suspenseful music playing]
[creaks again]
[blows]
[sighs softly]
[laughing]
Oh my gosh.
[fire crackling]
Hey.
[Rosie sighs]
I've been thinking about doing something.
It's not what people expect from me.
It's not even what I expected from me.
And, uh, it scares me.
In a good way.
Is it... [whispers] ...murder?
No, Cliff, it's not murder.
Then you're good!
Seriously.
If it comes from the real you,
it's gonna be amazing.
[exhales]
Have you ever heard of the bagworm moth?
No? Okay, so the female
builds this little house
out of silk and twigs,
carries it everywhere.
She hides in it her whole life.
But when she's ready...
she just burns it down and flies.
So, your pep talk is...
"Don't be a worm?"
My pep talk is "Don't hide.
Not when you've got wings."
Thanks, Cliff.
Anytime.
Oh, uh, just checking.
Still not in love with me though, right?
[laughs]
Give it time.
Girls love a project.
[laughs]
[phone ringing]
[sighs] Come on.
Oh, the rocks. So cliche.
[Shane over phone] Hey, Lark.
What's going on?
Shane, hi.
Oh... Yes! Finally.
How is the reconnecting going?
Please tell me you guys are bursting
with brotherly love.
[Shane] Well, we're at least talking
to each other.
[Nate] On a trial basis.
- I'll take it.
- How's the competition going?
[signal breaking up]
No, no, no, no, no, no, no. Hello? What?
[Nate] I said,
how's the competition going?
Really good, actually.
Yeah. Tomorrow is the second challenge,
it's gonna be all about performance.
I'm trying to find you guys
a triple threat opening act,
singing, dancing, star power.
[Nate] Love it. By the end
of this challenge, let's get down
to our final five competitors.
[breaking up]
What?
And make sure they have
the right attitude while performing.
- [bees buzzing]
- No matter what happens on stage,
the show must go on.
[Jason] What are you trying to say, Nate?
[Nate] What do you think
I'm trying to say, Jason?
Yeah, right attitude, final five.
Copy that. I gotta go, guys.
[♪ playing rock guitar chords]
Sounds good.
Thanks, man.
- You mind if I jump in?
- Let's do it.
'Kay. Where does it start?
- Right there.
- [♪ plays riff]
[♪ both jamming]
That right there
is why I love music. [laughs]
Same. That... That was awesome.
A true jam sesh, just messing around.
Jamming is great.
But I'm not here to mess around.
Ugh, you sound like Sage.
Knew I liked her.
Dude, don't talk about
my sister like that.
You telling me what to do?
No, sir.
[chuckles softly]
[PA chimes]
[Connie over PA] Time to rock and roll!
All those who've made it through
to the dance challenge,
please report to the flagpole.
Is Lark here?
[both] No.
[male camper] At least three
of these people have lice.
You're doing that wrong.
Good morning,
is what I would say
if I was a morning person.
[campers laughing]
[male camper] She's not a morning person.
So, last night,
we lost a couple of campers,
thanks to a smuggled phone.
- [crowd gasps]
- No way.
[Lark] Reminder.
No phones, no posts, no leaks.
This tour stays under wraps. You got it?
- Yes.
- Yeah.
My assistant Callie...
Technically I'm not
supposed to call her that.
Camper Callie is gonna lead us
in this dance challenge.
Grab a mic and a hat.
Follow me if you can.
No hats. If I see a fedora, you're donezo.
That's a threat!
I'm judging for overall star power.
You either got it or you don't.
Dance like no one is watching
except I'll be watching,
very closely.
Finally, my expertise.
If I tap you on the shoulder,
you are eliminated.
After this, we'll be down
to our final five.
Have fun.
- [♪ hip hop music playing]
- Ready?
♪ Come on! ♪
Let's go.
♪ First stop, hit the groove ♪
♪ Let the music play ♪
♪ Next stop, everybody ♪
♪ It's time to celebrate ♪
♪ Here we go so let your flow show ♪
♪ Make the dreams you got become real ♪
♪ Let's do this, let me hear you, now ♪
♪ Show me how you feel ♪
[chorus] ♪ Let's start, start
start the party ♪
♪ Come on, come on everyone ♪
♪ Let's start, start start the party ♪
♪ What you waiting for now? ♪
- I'm sorry.
- I just--
My condolences.
♪ Come on, come on live it up ♪
♪ Let's start, start start the party ♪
♪ I know you never gonna wanna stop ♪
♪ Let the music take us to paradise ♪
♪ Just close our eyes ♪
♪ Feel the groove wanna shake us ♪
♪ Everywhere and everybody ♪
♪ Turn it up
Let's start the party ♪
♪ Ooh ♪
♪ Pump, pump, pump, pump, pump ♪
♪ The party ♪
♪ We got it rolling
Never slowing down ♪
♪ Lights, camera, action
Start the party now ♪
♪ I know you're ready
There's no need to wait ♪
♪ Now's the time for us to celebrate ♪
♪ Start, start the party ♪
♪ Let's do it ♪
♪ Everybody now
Start, start the party ♪
- [Maddie gasps] Sage!
- [Sage] Desi, keep dancing.
You can't just stop dancing.
What?
- That's not fair.
- What? [groans]
♪ What you waiting for now? ♪
Wait!
No matter what, the show must go on.
No!
♪ Let's start, start start the party ♪
♪ Come on, come on everyone ♪
That's not fair! Maddie, Maddie, Maddie!
♪ Let's start, start start the party ♪
Get off of me!
What'd you do? Maddie, come back.
♪ Come on, come on
Live it up ♪
♪ Let's start, start start the party ♪
♪ I know you never gonna wanna ♪
♪ Come on let me hear you holler ♪
♪ Party's never ever gonna stop ♪
[all cheering]
And then there were five.
[cheering continues]
I know.
Desi, consider yourself lucky.
I'd work on your dance moves
if I were you.
- No, you did.
- [both laughing]
- I can't.
[scoffing]
I never thought Maddie the Baddie
would go down in a dance challenge.
And yet, balance is restored!
[laughs]
Speaking of baddies...
Callie, don't even...
Okay, look, I'm not saying
your brother is cute.
I'm just saying he's not, not cute.
[gags] Absolutely not.
Stop.
Sorry, we're closed.
I actually came to talk to Callie.
Go ahead.
Alone.
Okay.
[scoffs]
You're a really good dancer.
Agreed. Thank you.
Me not so much.
I was thinking
maybe you could help me out.
Give me a few... [whispers] ...lessons.
Wait, you want me to do what?
Please don't make me say it again.
So you're actually gonna compete?
Baby steps, Callie.
First, you gotta teach me how to dance.
Okay. But I'm not gonna go easy on you.
So get ready.
Cooler by the fire pit.
Come on! Don't eat all
the marshmallows, people.
Save it for tonight.
- [phone ringing]
- Why is it so hard?
[sighs]
Hey, Nate. What's going on?
Hey, Lark. Can you tell Shane
that the suits are happening.
He listens to you.
- [phone ringing]
- Hang on.
Hey, Shane.
Can you tell Nate
we're not dressing up as groomsmen.
You guys know you can say this
to each other directly.
We tried. It got loud.
- [cell phone vibrates]
- Hang on!
Jason, please tell me
this is not about wardrobe.
- No.
- Fantastic.
- Have you seen my child?
- Jason!
You know what?
I have had enough of you three.
Gentlemen, this is not
a conference call I asked for.
You are grown men. Use your words
with each other.
I just want us to look like
we belong up there.
And I just want us to feel like us,
- not the version everyone expects.
- [Lark] Figure it out, guys!
I'm about to produce
a bonfire for the first time.
And yes, there is a learning curve.
[sighs] I'm hanging up.
Wait, wait, wait.
How's the competition going?
Great.
We're down to our final five.
We just need to make sure they can really
handle being on tour.
Exactly. A successful tour is about
more than just talent.
[Jason] Yeah. Long nights,
tight spaces, terrible food.
They gotta be able to survive the grind.
And if they can handle that,
they can pretty much handle
being on the road.
Hmm. No, not again.
Oh, uh, update,
- I found the baby.
- Great.
You know what? I gotta go.
Canela. No, Emmy, drop the marshmallows!
[Sage singing] ♪ Most days I am inspired ♪
♪ Some days I am awake ♪
[♪ guitar strums]
♪ I'm confident and insecure
even at my best ♪
Not bad.
I'm still struggling with the lyrics.
You just gotta have fun with it.
[chuckles] You make it sound so easy.
All right, just so you know,
all of this isn't gonna distract me.
- All right? I'm in it to win it.
- So am I.
[chuckles softly]
Can I ask you something?
What's with you and your brother?
[sighs]
You picked up on that?
Yeah, it's kinda hard not to.
We used to be in a band together,
and then I left for Anthem.
I wanted to take my music seriously.
When the band broke up,
it kind of felt like we did, too.
[sighs]
Can I ask you something?
If you must.
Are you really the bad boy
everyone says you are?
Define bad.
You showed up to camp in a cop car.
[laughs]
[clicks tongue]
Um, truth is, I came straight from court.
My mom passed away in March,
and it was always just me and her,
and now it's just me.
[clicks tongue]
A judge is figuring out where I go next.
Fletch, I'm so sorry.
But I'm really glad you're here.
[Cliff singing] ♪ Sage and Fletch
sitting in a-- ♪
Shoot!
Guys, a little help?
- You hungry?
- Starving.
Come on. How am I supposed
to get back to shore?
I can't swim.
[Fletch] Yeah, you can, Cliff.
[Cliff] I know I can. But I don't want to.
- Stay vigilant.
- Mmm.
Revenge is near.
[chuckles]
- Oh.
- It's a zombie. I still need to glaze it.
Impressive.
[clears throat]
Maddie, can we go over the plan again?
They each got the message
that Lark wanted a style consult.
They'll be here any minute.
- Wait, are you sure we shou--
- Don't gaslight me, Daniel.
Mmm.
They sabotaged us in the dance challenge.
We are not the problem here.
- Mmm-mmm.
- They are.
We bring joy to millions
with our joyful content that promotes joy.
But somehow those five
are the chosen ones?
I don't think so.
[chattering indistinctly]
What are you guys doing here?
Welcome to your style consult.
Lark didn't call you here. We did.
We thought you all needed
more elevated looks, you know,
so your performances will really pop.
All of you needed serious redesigning.
Desi,
you'll never have what it takes
to shine on stage.
But, hey, at least your sneakers will.
Fletch.
Some preschool realness
for our mysterious musician.
- Cliff.
- [Cliff] My drumsticks!
Now, they're as weird as you are.
Fix your branding problem, Sage.
This is next level petty, Madison!
Whatever major loser!
And you know, Rosie,
classical music is just so stuffy.
I thought I'd help you with that.
You bedazzled my cello!
Watch out! Metronome Mary is angry.
[gasps]
Nobody talks to Rosie like that!
- [Fletch] Cliff!
- [♪ pop rock music playing, "It's On"]
♪ I hope you're ready
for the time of your life ♪
♪ Just look at me
I put a gleam in your eye ♪
[laughing wickedly]
♪ Buckle up ♪
[gasps]
♪ We're gonna take you for a ride ♪
Okay, now, it's on!
[all yelling]
♪ Let's go, we gotcha goin'
get in the vibe ♪
- ♪ Everybody put your hands to the sky ♪
- Cliff!
[laughs mischievously]
♪ Buckle up, we're gonna
take you, take you high ♪
- ♪ Ah-ooh ♪
- [Sage] Nice, Rosie!
♪ Show me, show me show me... ♪
Desi, help me.
♪ C'mon, c'mon, c'mon,
c'mon, ready or not ♪
♪ La-la-la-la-la-la
let me see how you vibe ♪
- ♪ It's on, it's on, it's on ♪
- [Sage] Go, Rosie!
♪ Get crazy, crazy, crazy
take it over the top ♪
I gotta admit, Fletch,
I'm a bit disappointed.
I expected more from a guy
with your reputation.
You know nothing about me, Madison.
- ♪ Okay, now ♪
- Watch out!
- [groaning]
- ♪ Are you ready? ♪
No!
♪ One, two
One, two, three, four! ♪
Guys, we gotta go now!
♪ 'Cause we, 'cause we ♪
♪ 'Cause when we rock we let it rock ♪
♪ Rock it, rock it rock it ♪
♪ Rock it, dance till we drop ♪
Um, guys?
[gasps]
♪ It's on! ♪
[groans]
[Lark] So, Connie spoke
to Madison's parents.
They'll be replacing
everything she trashed,
including your cello,
instead of buying her a car.
Justice! Sweet justice.
Uh-uh. Don't pat yourselves on the back.
You five weren't exactly
innocent bystanders, you were part of it.
It's like a glitter apocalypse.
Okay. Well, you saw what they did to
our stuff though, right?
We were just defending ourselves.
Yeah, my cello was vandalized.
I was simply avenging its honor.
I hear you, but it really doesn't matter.
This behavior is unacceptable on tour.
Okay, well, I didn't start it.
I was just avenging your honor.
Thank you, but I didn't ask you to.
Sage was the one who told me
to grab the paint.
Oh, so now you start listening to me?
Yeah, and at the end,
I was just defending Fletch.
- I can handle myself, okay?
- Yeah, but we're buddy.
[all shouting indistinctly]
Enough!
If you can't handle each other,
in an arts and crafts room,
how do you expect to survive here?
Welcome to your third and final challenge.
The camp bus?
We must get rid of them.
And I know exactly how to do it.
Lark is not gonna be happy when she finds
a video of the third challenge
posted by the final five.
That'll ruin the whole competition.
What a shame! [laughs wickedly]
[Daniel] But they wouldn't post a video.
They'd be disqualified.
- I'm posting the video, Daniel.
- Oh!
Now, go sneak into Connie's office
and get my phone.
-On it. Let's go, Danielle
-Ugh.
Here it is! Your home
for the next 24 hours.
Twenty-four hours?
- So we have to sleep on this bus?
- [Lark] Yep.
But Final Jam's in two days.
I've got stuff to do.
Prep here then. Because this is about
more than just music.
It's about proving
you can handle tour life.
The challenge is just to sit here?
Not just sit, stay.
If anyone steps off this bus,
you're eliminated!
[scoffing]
Is there even a bathroom on here?
Ta da!
[Cliff] Oh come on!
A porta-potty in the summer
is basically a poop oven.
So you have been to Coachella.
I can't. Porta-potties are my nightmare.
Yeah. She got locked inside one
at a soccer field for like an hour.
Yeah, because you told Dad
I was at a playdate.
Technically, you were.
Just you and the toilet though.
Okay, we're done here.
FYI, this is what touring feels like.
No privacy, tight spaces,
annoying people breathing your air.
If you want to survive out there,
learn to survive in here.
[♪ instrumental rock music playing]
[laughing]
[chuckles]
Cliff...
It's time.
Don't let anyone open it.
And make sure nobody knocks it over.
Roger that. You can count on me.
Okay.
[♪ suspenseful music playing]
[whispers] Come on.
Were you able to secure the contraband
from Connie's office?
I have no idea what that means.
- [sighs]
- Yeah. Wait, why are we doing this again?
Because, Daniel,
sometimes karma needs a little push.
I want them disqualified.
[gasps] Oh, wow.
- You really hate them.
- I don't
use the word hate, Danielle?
[clears throat]
I simply release people
who no longer serve my journey.
I release them really hard.
[laughing maniacally]
Calm down, Danielle.
Can you not...
[snoring]
[sighs]
How can he sleep so well in here?
[snoring continues]
[choking]
[screams, pants]
[sputters]
I had the most horrible dream, guys.
I couldn't breathe.
- Really? That's so weird.
- [breathing heavily]
Rosie. You can't suffocate Cliff.
No, I didn't try to--
I wasn't suffocating Cliff.
I just wanted him to stop breathing, okay?
A little.
Just making sure you guys haven't gone
all Lord of the Flies on me.
What's Lord of the Flies?
- Read a book, Cliff.
- No, we're good.
- Yeah, we're good.
- Yeah, I'm good.
Cool. Don't burn the place down.
See you in the morning.
Girl, you've got to hold it together.
[whimpers]
Uh...
[Sage] Come on, let's go see what's wrong.
[sniffles]
Rosie...
are you okay?
I don't know.
All I know is that
I need to win this.
I need to go on tour.
Because what if when I go home,
I go back to being the old Rosie?
That Rosie was perfectly content
performing classical music with her cello.
She never even dared to dream bigger.
But here at Camp Rock,
I've finally felt what it's like to be
in the spotlight and...
I think I love it.
I don't know. Just, like the thought
of going back
to the orchestra I just get so...
- Nervous?
- Angry?
Depressed?
Stunning?
[all laughing]
I don't want to go back home either.
My parents, my teachers,
my classmates...
I know they all think I'm too much,
so music's always been my only friend.
Not anymore.
- We're buddies, remember?
- Yeah.
Cliff, I'll jam with you anytime.
I mean, hello!
You are my porta-potty security guard.
We're bonded for life.
Cliff, you threw paste
in an influencers face for me.
Of course I'm your friend.
[chuckles softly]
Rosie, you know how
you just found the spotlight,
I've wanted it my whole life.
I've been so focused chasing the dream.
But here, it feels like
I'm already living it.
Yeah, because here you don't have to be
a musical tyrant all the time.
[laughs]
I'm just saying that at camp,
the music is the goal.
Okay, fair.
But that goes out the window
when you're competing
for the gig of a lifetime.
That's what scares me. [scoffs]
I love the magic of music,
but if I win, it's not just
about the music anymore.
It's about being good enough
for Connect 3.
Making music is easy.
Being their opener...
that's hard.
What?
Uh, alright.
Um... [clears throat]
Being at camp is a lot easier
than the rest of my life.
I don't exactly know
what my future looks like.
But as long as I'm either here
or hopefully on tour, um,
all I gotta worry about is my music.
[Cliff] Look at us.
We're just five puzzle pieces
that shouldn't fit,
but somehow we do.
[♪ percussive music playing]
♪ We walk the walk
We talk the talk ♪
♪ We're the kids of Camp Rock ♪
[all] ♪ We walk the walk
We talk the talk ♪
♪ We're the kids of Camp Rock, whoo! ♪
[♪ Sage vocalizing]
♪ Yeah ♪
♪ I hear it in my head
like an echo, echo ♪
♪ A song I can't forget
don't wanna let go, let go ♪
♪ And every person that I found ♪
♪ Is a melody that sticks around ♪
♪ Like an e-e-e-echo ♪
♪ Like an echo ♪
♪ Sometimes I don't know
the way even up from down ♪
♪ I guess I don't know how to fake it ♪
♪ But I turn around and ♪
♪ You're right there
making a joke about it ♪
♪ With a little spark in your eye ♪
♪ Take lemons
and make something out of it ♪
♪ It's just a start ♪
♪ But I hear it in my head
like an echo, echo ♪
♪ A song I can't forget
don't wanna let go let go ♪
♪ And every person that I found ♪
♪ Is a melody that sticks around ♪
♪ Like an e-e-e-echo ♪
♪ Like an echo ♪
♪ Swear I could write a thousand lines ♪
♪ About what I'm scared of ♪
♪ But face it now
I'mma find the light ♪
♪ Maybe I am strong enough ♪
♪ Keep going
I like the sound of it ♪
♪ Let's make it loud
'cause I hear it in my head ♪
- ♪ Like an echo, echo ♪
- ♪ I hear it ♪
♪ A song I can't forget
don't wanna let go, let go ♪
♪ And every person that I found ♪
♪ Is a melody that sticks around ♪
♪ Like an e-e-e-echo ♪
♪ Like an echo ♪
[all laughing]
[snores]
[Sage] I'll never get over these stars.
I wish summer lasted forever.
Hello?
Earth to Fletch.
Sorry.
What were you thinking about?
Nothing.
Those eyes are dangerous.
[both laughing]
Um...
I was just
thinking about how winning
this competition could...
It could really fix everything.
I still have no idea where
I'm gonna be living after camp
but my cousin's fighting it for me.
I'm just waiting on the call to find out
where I'm headed next.
That's why I have this.
Well, I'm glad they let you
keep your phone.
Oh.
They didn't exactly let me keep my phone.
I showed up after registration
and no one asked.
Please don't...
Please don't say anything.
I won't.
[shivers]
Are you cold?
I'm good.
Right.
[laughs]
- Thanks. I appreciate it.
- Mm-hmm.
[owl hooting]
Why do you always sing
with your eyes closed?
Don't you want to connect with
the people in the audience?
And why?
They all leave after the show anyways.
I don't know, I...
I don't want the people
that I share a connection with to just...
leave.
Yeah, but what if it's worth it
to really connect with someone?
Even if it's only for one song.
[car horn honks]
- [others in bus] Cliff!
- [Cliff] Whoops! Sorry.
[both laughing]
[birds chirping]
[snoring]
[whistle blows]
Oh good. You guys are awake.
Your 24 hours are up.
Is this real or am I still hallucinating?
This is very real. You're done!
Final Jam is tomorrow night.
That means you have
one day left to work on your songs.
Don't waste it.
You know where to find me.
Is it weird that I'm kinda
gonna miss this bus?
Not weird.
Same here.
[Sage] So we make a pact,
whatever happens, we stay in touch.
[Cliff] Great. First order of business...
[yawns] Group chat name?
How about...
Cliff and the Cliffhangers?
- [all chuckle]
- Cliff.
We'll workshop it later.
[sighing]
I know that notebook.
Oh, wow. I have not seen it in so long.
It's been years.
I found it hidden in my cabin.
Whenever Mitchie
was dealing with something
or feeling something,
she just had to write about it.
It helped her figure things out.
Yeah, that's exactly
what it's been doing for me.
- Yeah?
- Yeah.
[chuckles softly]
But here. She probably wants it back.
- How about you take care of it for her?
- Really?
I think Mitchie would want it
to stay at Camp Rock.
With someone who needs it
just as much as she did.
How's the songwriting coming?
I'm not quite there yet.
That's okay.
It's a work in progress.
[♪ piano music playing]
[mumbling indistinctly]
[laughs, applauds]
Okay!
Go away.
When did you learn to dance?
Mmm, since you ditched me and the band,
I had a lot of free time.
I didn't ditch you. I just...
I wanted more than the garage.
Yeah, well, when you left for more,
you left me, too.
- Desi--
- I miss being your bandmate, Sage.
And your brother.
- In that order.
- [laughs]
Okay, so maybe we try again?
Different stage, bigger crowd.
You know, this could be our reunion tour.
Come on, band mates for life.
[laughing]
[♪ upbeat music playing]
♪ Mmm, mmm, mmm, mmm ♪
♪ Yeah, yeah, yeah ♪
♪ Okay, so maybe I'm stubborn
tried to be tougher ♪
♪ But maybe it ain't always
gotta be like that ♪
♪ Been a little self-centered ♪
♪ You don't know the pressure
I was under ♪
♪ When you wouldn't hit me back ♪
♪ You talk fast when you're wrong ♪
♪ You hold grudges too long ♪
♪ Driving me insane! ♪
♪ Sorry for the cold shoulder ♪
♪ If I could do it over ♪
♪ I would go back
and take more of the blame ♪
♪ No matter how much that we're fightin' ♪
♪ And boy, don't you know
that we tried it ♪
♪ No matter how hard we deny it ♪
♪ Deny it ♪
♪ We got the same back beat heartbeat ♪
♪ No one do it like we do ♪
♪ We got the same tempo in our bones
Rockin' it like a groove ♪
♪ Ooh, we've been through a lot ♪
♪ Kinda hate that it's true ♪
♪ We got the same
back beat, heartbeat, yeah ♪
- ♪ Rhythm's only right with ♪
- ♪ Only right with ♪
♪ You, you, you, you ♪
♪ All the late nights ♪
♪ Always get into fights ♪
♪ But no one understands me like you do ♪
♪ Just keep on ♪
♪ Keep on rolling your eyes ♪
♪ You're stuck in this band for life ♪
♪ In the end
I'm glad it's me and you ♪
♪ Because we got the same
back beat, heart beat ♪
♪ No one do it like we do ♪
♪ We got the same tempo in our bones ♪
♪ Rockin' it like a groove ♪
♪ Ooh, we've been through a lot ♪
♪ Kinda hate that it's true ♪
♪ We got the same back beat heartbeat ♪
♪ Yeah, yeah
The rhythm's only right with ♪
♪ Only right with you, you, you, you ♪
♪ Rhythm's only with you ♪
[PA chimes]
[Connie] Will the final five
of the competition
please report to my office?
Any idea what this is about?
No idea.
Come on in.
Have a seat.
I know that one of you has a phone.
Who is it?
You knew the rule.
No phones, no posting, no excuses.
I could disqualify all of you.
No!
[exhales]
[tapping nervously]
Well, I haven't seen my phone
since I turned it in.
Don't look at me.
My mom won't even let me have a phone.
She thinks I have focus issues,
which is ridiculous.
Sorry.
I may not take things seriously,
but I wouldn't break this rule.
That leaves you two.
[Lark] Guys, the competition's
on the line.
Connect 3 still needs an opening act.
Fletch... just tell them.
Are you being serious?
What is she talking about?
[sighs]
Uh...
[scoffs]
[groans softly]
I hope you're happy with yourself, Fletch.
A video of all of you singing on the bus
has already gone viral.
Yeah. I've been doing
damage control all day.
The brothers are not happy about this.
The competition was supposed
to be a big reveal.
No, wait! He...
He would never do that.
Everyone out!
Fletch, you stay.
- Fletch.
- [Connie] Sage.
- Go.
- [Fletch] Connie, it wasn't me, I swear.
[Connie] Well, if you didn't
post it, Fletch, then who did?
[♪ guitar strumming]
Be honest. Am I the worst?
Define worst.
Desi, be serious.
I mean, did Fletch have a phone?
Yeah.
But did you have to tell Connie about it?
I mean, we were all
gonna get disqualified.
I couldn't risk not competing.
I mean, everything I've ever worked for
would've been for nothing.
But... I did regret it after I said it.
Do you think he'll ever forgive me?
I forgave you, didn't I?
Sage, I love how ambitious you are.
Honestly, I've been trying
to be a little more like you lately.
[chuckles softly]
But you did choose Anthem over me.
And now you chose
the competition over Fletch.
I've just always put my dream
before everything else.
My music was all I ever needed.
But this time, it's the everything else
that I can't stop thinking about.
Everything or everyone?
I think the the studio here
looks a lot nicer than when we were here.
I know, it's insane.
They have four engineers.
Hold on. Lark.
Oh, hey, guys!
Sorry, I can't really talk right now.
You have me producing Final Jam
which is like a billion tiny shows in one
on a summer camp's budget. So...
We're pretty familiar
with what the Final Jam is.
Well, get ready for my Final Jam.
Lark, you let your hair down, literally.
How nice of you to notice, Jason.
I have bug bites on my bug bites
and a lot to discuss with my therapist.
You'll be getting the invoice.
Oh, come on, you're gonna miss this place.
You know you are.
I guess the songs are kinda catchy.
You know what? I don't have time for this.
I'm busy. I'll see you later.
Don't be late.
I saw that smile.
[Shane] You think we pay her enough?
- [Nate] Probably not.
- [Shane] How many bug bites?
Wow.
This view never gets old.
It is so good to be back,
especially with you guys.
I just can't believe
little Lennon McCartney
gets to spend every summer here.
I can't believe you named
your kid Lennon McCartney.
Two of the greatest
songwriters of all time.
Yeah, but, like, pick one.
Guys, guys, the important thing
is we're gonna find our new opening act.
- One.
- Two.
- No! Hey, no! [groans]
- [water splashing]
Enjoy the swim!
[Shane] Oh, Come on! Guys, my hair!
[Shane groans]
Oh. I love being reconnected.
- Me too, bro.
- [Shane] Come on! Bring me a towel!
So you can peel it off
and put it in between--
But that's just too messy.
- There's no perfect s'mores.
- S'mores supposed to be messy.
- [Rosie] Because it--
- [Cliff] I get you--
- Hey, guys.
- [all] Hi.
- Hey.
- Fletch, can I talk to you?
- Okay, so, like...
- Yeah.
- ...when you get like the burntness...
[sighs]
- All right, about the video--
- Sage, it's fine.
No! I need to say this.
Look, I know you wouldn't do that.
I just... I-I panicked,
and I didn't trust you
and I should have. That's on me.
You broke a rule, yeah, but I broke
something bigger,
and I thought I was protecting
my shot at the competition,
and all I did was prove
that I didn't believe
in the people I care about.
Are you done? [chuckles]
Thank you. Seriously.
And you're right, it wasn't me.
Connie and Lark traced it,
and the video came from Madison's account.
I'm re-instated. [chuckles]
We're all still in.
Oh, Fletch, that's so great.
[Cliff, Rosie, and Desi laughing]
- [Desi and Rosie laugh]
- [Cliff] So funny...
[Connie] All right, ladies.
[Lark] Final Jam is tonight.
[Connie] Oh. [laughs] I think they know.
- [Lark] Stay vigilant.
- [Connie] Thank you, ladies.
We'll put one in the center,
and the other one can go
right here by the speakers.
[chattering indistinctly]
[♪ upbeat music playing]
You can put the mic with the keyboard.
Thank you.
Psst.
Mom.
- [laughs]
- [Connie] Mitchie!
- Oh!
- Surprise!
A day off from tour,
I couldn't miss Final Jam.
Come sit in the front row.
Oh, they'll go crazy.
No, no, no, this is their night, not mine.
[sighs] You'll always be Camp Rock star.
And now it's their turn.
Go.
I'll see you after?
[all cheering]
Let's hear it, Camp Rock!
Welcome to Final Jam.
It's Shane Gray for crying out loud!
- I know.
- Who's ready to help us
pick our opening act?
[all cheering]
You know her.
You fear her.
And you've probably
been eliminated by her.
Make some noise for your Final Jam emcee,
- Lark.
- Whoo!
[all cheering]
When I say final, you say jam.
- Final.
- [crowd] Jam.
- Jam.
Okay, that's enough.
Our first competitor
has rhythm in his bones,
drumsticks in his pockets,
and absolutely no off switch.
But that's just the way we like him.
Make some noise for Cliff Carmichael!
[all cheering]
Ready to rock, are you?
♪ Bounce to the beat
Bo-bounce to the beat ♪
[beatboxing]
[all cheering]
♪ They say that I'm a glitch
Say I do too many bits ♪
♪ Some folks call me a llama ♪
♪ 'Cause they hate it when I spit ♪
♪ They say "Cliff you're too much ♪
♪ Your music is too loud" ♪
♪ They say I rock the boat ♪
♪ But I'm just trying to rock the crowd ♪
♪ I've heard it all before ♪
♪ So you can call me what you want to ♪
♪ Sticks and stones may break my bones ♪
♪ But sticks can also
One-two! ♪
♪ I don't want it
If it's not a little crazy ♪
♪ Say I'm strange
Pu-pu-pu-pu-puh ♪
♪ Nuh-uh-uh  ♪
♪ No, I don't wanna fit in ♪
♪ Bounce to the beat
Bo-Bounce to the beat ♪
♪ Of my own drum ♪
♪ I don't wanna
You know you can't restrain me ♪
♪ Ooh-whee
I just wanna have fun ♪
♪ Nuh-uh-uh
No, I don't wanna fit in ♪
♪ Bounce to the beat
Bo-bounce to the beat ♪
♪ Of my own drum ♪
♪ Bounce to the beat
Bo-bounce to the beat ♪
[trills]
[all cheering]
I guess you could say
our next competitor had me at "cello."
[crickets chirping]
Tough crowd. Make some noise
for Rosie Kleinman.
[all cheering]
[♪ dramatic string music playing]
[all gasping]
♪ I wore the smile they picked for me ♪
♪ Hit every note and line so clean ♪
♪ Bit my tongue till it turned blue ♪
♪ Played pretend like they told me to ♪
♪ They want a soul sweet and small ♪
♪ But I was born to burn it all ♪
♪ Now I'm tearing up your script ♪
♪ Watch me flip the switch ♪
♪ Click, click ♪
♪ Plug me in
I'm a live explosive ♪
♪ Broke the box and recomposed it ♪
♪ I don't perform
I detonate ♪
♪ I pull the pin
Now get out of the way ♪
♪ I play it loud
I play it raw ♪
♪ I play it real
I play it far ♪
♪ Turned my cello into a flame ♪
♪ This is my sound
and I'll play it my way ♪
♪ I'll bend the strings
I'll make it scream ♪
♪ This time I'll play for bigger things ♪
♪ No bowing down
No sweet ballet ♪
♪ This is my song
And I'll play it my way ♪
[♪ string music continues]
♪ Whoa-oh ♪
♪ This is my sound
And I'll play it my way ♪
[all cheering]
Give it up for Desi Scott.
Whoo!
[♪ funky music playing]
♪ All my life, gettin' by non-committal ♪
♪ Never like competing
with everyone else ♪
♪ Maybe I'll let it slide just a little ♪
♪ 'Cause when I take
a real hard look at myself ♪
♪ You wanna sing the spotlight
or the audience? ♪
♪ If it's my shot then I won't miss ♪
♪ Out the way now I'm coming through ♪
♪ When the song starts to play
You hit the center stage, yeah ♪
♪ Get ready, get ready ♪
♪ I'm putting on a show
and you don't even know ♪
♪ So, get ready, get ready ♪
♪ Ready to lead the pack in a minute ♪
♪ Nothing can hold me back
Now I'm in it ♪
♪ Oh, it feels so right
Watch me come alive ♪
♪ Better get ready
Get ready, get ready ♪
♪ I know it's been a long time coming ♪
♪ Don't let it slip away ♪
♪ Bet I'm gonna say something ♪
♪ If you underestimate ♪
♪ I ain't gonna waste time waste time ♪
♪ I'll be up in your face
with the boom and the bass line ♪
♪ So get ready
Get ready, get ready ♪
♪ When the song starts to play
you hit the center stage ♪
♪ Get ready, get ready, get ready ♪
♪ I'm putting on a show
And you don't even know ♪
♪ So get ready get ready ♪
♪ Ready to lead the pack in a minute ♪
♪ Nothing can hold me back
Now I'm in it ♪
♪ Oh, it feels so right
Watch me come alive ♪
♪ Better get ready get ready, get ready ♪
[♪ vocalizing]
♪ Get ready, ready
Yeah ♪
[all cheering]
You know, he hadn't danced
before he came to Camp Rock.
- What? Are you serious?
- Really?
- This place is amazing.
- Reminds me of a much younger,
younger, younger, younger version of you.
Let's hear it for Camp Rock's
very own Fletch Robinson!
[all applauding]
[Fletch] One, two, three, four.
♪ Felt like I was in a world alone ♪
♪ Until I found a part of it
to call my own ♪
♪ Missing moments
when I kept my eyes closed ♪
♪ But you can make the strangest places ♪
♪ Feel like home ♪
♪ You got all my colors running true ♪
♪ The highs and lows
we've both been through ♪
Open your eyes. Open your eyes.
♪ I finally found someone to see it too ♪
♪ Well, I know tomorrow ♪
♪ We'll wake up on the bright side ♪
♪ Chase away all the dark nights ♪
♪ And find a way to hope ♪
♪ I know tomorrow ♪
♪ We'll feel something so brand new ♪
♪ Leave our past in the rear view ♪
♪ Say it's gonna get better ♪
♪ I know tomorrow, tomorrow ♪
♪ I know tomorrow ♪
♪ Oh, it all happens for a reason ♪
♪ The alchemy of heartbreak
Time to go ♪
♪ What's around the corner
I won't fear it ♪
♪ 'Cause I'm not alone ♪
♪ I know tomorrow ♪
♪ We'll wake up on the bright side ♪
♪ Chase away all the dark nights ♪
♪ And find a way to hope ♪
♪ I know tomorrow ♪
♪ We'll feel something so brand new ♪
♪ Leave our past in the rear view ♪
♪ And say it's gonna get better ♪
♪ I know tomorrow, tomorrow ♪
♪ I know tomorrow ♪
[all cheering]
[fan] Fletch!
Our final competitor came here
with something to prove.
Please put your hands together
for Sage Scott!
[all cheering]
[♪ slow music playing]
- It's okay.
- [♪ music stops]
[Sage] It's okay.
I've spent my whole life
working towards an opportunity like this.
Opening for Connect 3,
it's a dream come true.
But this summer
with these four people,
made me realize
that winning this competition
isn't why I came to Camp Rock.
They are.
[♪ sentimental music playing]
[inaudible]
You should pick Cliff.
Because you'll never see another like him.
[inaudible]
[chuckles]
Or Rosie
because she didn't just
join this competition.
She... She brought it.
[inaudible]
Pick Fletch because it turns out
his music's more true than his reputation.
[inaudible]
Pick Desi because he's got the heart
of a rock star.
[inaudible]
Anyway,
this is my song.
It's not what I planned, but...
the best melodies never are.
♪ Most days I am inspired
Some days I am a wreck ♪
♪ I'm confident and insecure
even at my best ♪
♪ My journal is my secret
I write in it every day ♪
[crowd cheering]
♪ All of the dreams
I dream about ♪
♪ Will happen
I know, someday ♪
♪ As I paint my life
my canvas stretches wide ♪
♪ And my masterpiece
I'll draw outside the lines ♪
♪ And I do my best to be my best ♪
♪ Even if I fail ♪
♪ What I'll learn
I'll turn into ♪
♪ The wind in my sails ♪
♪ It's the story of my life ♪
[crowd cheers]
♪ But at least I've got time ♪
♪ I'm a work in progress ♪
♪ And I've got a plan ♪
♪ It's written in ink ♪
♪ On the back of my hand ♪
♪ If I'm being honest ♪
♪ Who I am is undefined ♪
♪ But that's all right ♪
♪ I'm not perfect but nobody is ♪
♪ And just like a wild flower
caught in the wind ♪
♪ It's a journey ♪
♪ And I'm loving
all the twists and the turns ♪
♪ Even though it hurts ♪
♪ My story's still unwritten ♪
♪ And they are teardrops on the page ♪
♪ I don't know where I fit in ♪
♪ But I love the friends
I've made ♪
♪ I won't give up what I want most ♪
♪ Even on my darkest days
I don't lose hope, no ♪
♪ I might not always be right
but I'm gonna try, oh ♪
♪ It's a work in progress ♪
♪ And I got a plan ♪
♪ It's written in ink
on the back of my hand ♪
♪ If I'm being honest ♪
♪ Who I am is undefined ♪
♪ But that's all right ♪
♪ I'm not perfect
But nobody is ♪
♪ And just like a wild flower
caught in the wind ♪
♪ It's a journey ♪
♪ And I'm loving
all the twists and the turns ♪
♪ Even though it hurts ♪
♪ We doubt, we trust
We feel too much ♪
♪ Our future's in the distance
Oh, yeah ♪
- ♪ We make mistakes ♪
♪ Our hearts will break ♪
♪ Our story's still unwritten ♪
♪ And we're not perfect
But nobody is ♪
♪ Just like a wild flower
caught in the wind ♪
♪ It's a journey ♪
♪ I'm loving all the twists
and the turns ♪
♪ Oh ♪
♪ We're a work in progress ♪
[♪ vocalizing]
♪ It's a work in progress ♪
♪ Hey ♪
♪ I guess we're just ♪
♪ A work in progress ♪
[crowd cheering]
Wow.
So I guess the video
we posted didn't work.
[scoffing]
Nice going, Danielle.
Maddie.
Wait, guys!
Okay, how are we supposed
to pick just one?
Yeah, they should all be out there.
Choosing one feels like
we're telling the other four
they're not good enough
That's just not true.
[Mitchie] Don't tell me
you guys still can't agree on anything.
- No way.
- Hi, guys.
Are you kidding me?
I thought you were still on tour.
You didn't think I'd miss this, did you?
Oh, my gosh, that was the best
Final Jam I've ever seen.
They were all incredible.
And that girl at the end, Sage,
she's really good.
So, Sage?
It's not just about one person.
It's about the way
they make each other shine.
No stage tricks, no spotlight,
just music, pure and real.
Reminds me of us back then.
Just kids who couldn't
stop playing together.
Totally. But we still got
to pick one of them.
Are you sure about that?
[crowd cheering]
All right, all right.
We came here to pick our opening act.
But with the help of an old friend,
we realized something.
What we saw tonight
was more than just one person.
And because of that,
- we can't pick a single one of you.
- [crowd gasps]
[all murmuring indistinctly]
[Shane] So...
we're going to choose all of you.
That's right.
We want all of you as a group!
[crowd cheering]
- No way!
- [laughs] Oh, my God!
Whoo!
[all cheering]
You think they know what they just got?
Not yet, but they will.
- [Desi] We're going on tour!
- What?
[all cheering]
This place is still magical.
I guess some things never change.
So, same time next summer?
You're on.
[all applauding]
[♪ upbeat music playing]
[indistinct conversation]
[Rosie] We did it! We did it! Yeah!
- [whoops]
- [Desi] We did it! We did it!
Oh, okay.
Come on.
♪ 'Cause we rock... ♪
All right, let's roll.
♪ We rock, we rock on ♪
♪ Come as you are
You're a superstar ♪
♪ World's in your pocket and you know it ♪
♪ You can feel that beat
runnin' through your feet ♪
♪ You're heart's racing fast
You're rock 'n' rollin' ♪
♪ All that you need is the music ♪
♪ To take you to some other place ♪
♪ Where you know you belong ♪
♪ Raise your hands up
in the air and scream ♪
♪ We're finding our voice
Followin' our dreams ♪
♪ 'Cause we rock, we rock
We rock, we rock on ♪
♪ Nobody in the world's
gonna bring us down ♪
♪ The louder we go
Well, the better we sound ♪
♪ 'Cause we rock, we rock
We rock, we rock on ♪
♪ We rock, we rock
Camp Rock! ♪
[all cheering]
♪ Turn on the radio ♪
♪ As loud as it can go ♪
♪ Want to dance until my feet
can't feel the ground ♪
♪ Say goodbye to all my fears ♪
♪ One good song they disappear ♪
♪ And nothing in the world
can bring me down ♪
♪ Hand-clapping, hips shaking
Heart-breaking ♪
♪ There's no faking what you feel ♪
♪ When you're right at home ♪
♪ Yeah ♪
♪ Music's in my soul ♪
♪ I can hear it every day
and every night ♪
♪ It's the one thing on my mind ♪
♪ Music's got control ♪
♪ And I'm never letting go
No, no ♪
♪ I just wanna play my music ♪
♪ Got my six string on my back ♪
♪ Don't need anything but that ♪
♪ Everything I want is here with me ♪
[in operatic voice]
♪ So forget that fancy car ♪
[in techno voice]
♪ I don't need to go that far ♪
[pop style singing] ♪ What's driving me
is following my dream ♪
[vocalizing] ♪ Yeah ♪
[awkwardly] ♪ Hand clapping earthshaking ♪
♪ Heartbreaking
There's no faking ♪
[R&B style singing] ♪ What you feel
when you're on a roll ♪
♪ Yeah ♪
[pop style singing] ♪ Music's in my soul ♪
♪ I can hear it ♪
[Latin American style singing]
♪ Every day and every night ♪
♪ It's the one thing on my mind ♪
- ♪ Music's got control ♪
- [rapping] ♪ Music's got control y'all ♪
♪ Never let it go, no ♪
[jazz style] ♪ Oh no, no I just wanna
play my music ♪
[rock style singing]
♪ Music's got control ♪
♪ And I'm never letting go
No, no ♪
♪ I just wanna play my music ♪
♪ All night long ♪
♪ Yeah ♪